<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages]]></description>
        <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:39:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://agrihoodsglobal.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:39:13 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages features Soil Secrets LLC products!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<a href="https://soilsecrets.com/" data-role="cta">SOIL SECRETS LLC</a>,<h2><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages features Soil Secrets LLC products!</strong></em></h2>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> has partnered with <strong>Soil Secrets LLC</strong> to offer a ‘premium professional soil treatment inocula’ line of products designed to stimulate healthy soils!</p>,<p>There are essential biochemical processes necessary for optimal plant nutrition. This premium product line meets the benchmark of the <em>USDA National Organic Program</em> (NOP), and are available for use on organic certified farms.</p>,<p>Urban gardens and lawns may safely access <strong>Soil Secrets</strong> products for optimal plant and sod health! Rest assured that these plant-derived, organic treatment essentials actually serve Mother Earth, her “soil food web”, and any plants or crops grown!</p>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3929f03e2233d781c842f309d98ea09c73807729.png" title="SOIL SECRETS: &quot;Unlocking the Secrets to a Healthy Soil&quot;" alt="Soil Secrets LLC develops products that instigate the natural biochemical process required for healthy soils and proper plant nutrition.

Humates

All Soil Secrets products meet the benchmark of the USDA National Organic Program, and with Certifier approval, can be used on Organic Certified farms. The products are also safe for use on home gardens and lawns, without the fear of damaging the environment or exposing our bodies to hazardous chemicals. Our products are used in the construction and maintenance of landscapes, golf courses, mine reclamation, highway re-vegetation and farming. Benefits of Soil Secrets products include:

&bull; Improved water drought tolerance of crops, sports  fields, etc.
&bull; Improvement of water storage in soils.
&bull; Greener more environmentally sound landscapes.
&bull; Remediates toxic mine tailings, Total Petroleum  Hydrocarbons in soil, and jump starts healthy mutualistic soil biology for plants.

In addition, Soil Secrets science in Humic Acids is the best in the world, using a &ldquo;Commercial Proprietary Information Contract&rdquo; at the National Labs. Soil Secrets owns the only molecular science on the species description of soil carbon molecules generically called humic acids (Acct#-483 715 for orders).">,<h3><em><strong>Benefits of Soil Secrets:</strong></em></h3>,<ul><li>Improved water drought tolerance for crop production!</li><li>Improved water storage in soil!</li><li>Optimal efficiency of photosynthesis!</li><li>Improved nutrient exchange!</li><li>Optimized local “soil food web”!</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4ed33dfa-7bbc-4fe6-bfe2-3fdf984ac430.png" title="Soil Secrets Premium Product Line: USDA Certified Biobased Product" alt="Biobased product, was defined by the United States Secretary of Agriculture in the Farm Security and Rural Investment Act of 2002 as follows, &quot;The term &lsquo;&lsquo;biobased product&rsquo;&rsquo; means a product determined by the Secretary to be a commercial or industrial product (other than food or feed) that is composed, in whole or in significant part, of biological products or renewable domestic agricultural materials (including plant, animal, and marine materials) or forestry materials OR an intermediate feedstock.">,<h3><strong>“Soil Food Web”</strong></h3>,<p><em>Green Pastures AgriVillage</em>s believes in the Soil Secrets premium product line. This amazing product line reveres the “soil food web”, network of ecosystems, which provides nutrient distribution for the multiple feeding levels found within Mother Earth – the “Soil Food Web”(SFW)!</p>,<p>The SFW refers to an earth-based ecosystem (“community of organisms”) where these biological beings live most or part of their lives in the soil (e.g. bioactivity). This is all happening below ground, containing diverse trophic or feeding systems. SFW holds symbiotic relationships with the environment, including plants and animals.</p>,<p>Further, there is an intricate level of bioactivity with transfers of energy, between multiple species, within a biologically based system (ecosystem).</p>,<p>Soil Secrets taps into the SFW:</p>,<p><em>1) Decreases water usage!</em></p>,<p><em>2)Supports drought resistance!</em></p>,<p><em>3) Increases plant health</em></p>,<p><em>4) Increases crop production yields</em></p>,<p><em>5) Optimized “Soil Food Web” conditioning</em></p>,<p><em>6) Decreased costs long term </em></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1b171c28-b78c-4de3-97af-9d22292eb451.jpg" title="Soil Secrets supports Humic Soil Production &amp; Overall Health" alt="Soil Secrets LLC develops products which instigate the natural biochemical process required for healthy soils. This process is referred to as the &lsquo;Soil Food Web&rsquo;. The foundation of the Soil Secrets protocol is based on Mycorrhizal fungi and Humic substances rich in Humic Acids. Soils of urban landscapes, farms and other sites are often deficient or completely lacking in Mycorrhizae and Humic substances. Individually and combined these products provide the primary benefits we are after, which includes better nutrition for the plant, better water management for the landscape or farm and the building of soil (Pedogenesis).
Interests: Erosion Control, Erosion Control Products, Mine Reclamation, Organic Farming, Organic Agriculture, Farming Soil, Organic Soil.">,<h3><em><strong>Applied Science of Humic Acids: TerraPro®</strong></em></h3>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em>, with the support of Soil Secrets, uses sound science to support healthy soils. Some of this sound science includes humic acids. Humic acids are essential to the best quality, healthy, rich, and most productive soils in the world!</p>,<p>Humic acids offer the capacity to actually build and condition the soil’s ecosystem, leading to an appearance of a very dark fertile quality. Humic acids are nature’s best chelators of ‘plant nutrient bioavailability’, and are “…essential for a healthy and productive soil”(J. Chemical Education, 12/2001).</p>,<p>With ‘humic acid enrichment’, microbes are nurtured within the “soil food web” (SFW) creating an environment favorable for maximized root growth (root zone). Therefore, essential water and trace elements have increased bioavailability within the SFW. Plants receive improved nutrition and overall health. Healthy plants are more “nutrient dense”, when filled with vitamins and minerals.</p>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> appreciates Soil Secrets’ ability to authentically honor the essential element of carbon, which is contained within soils, as humic acids. Humic acids have supramolecular capability for effectiveness in treatment for land remediation. Their ability for land remediation can counter toxins, corrosive materials, and even salty environments. This furtherimproves the SFW!</p>,<h2><em><strong>Soil Secrets Benefits:</strong></em></h2>,<ul><li><em>Improves nutrient uptake!</em></li><li><em>Improves “SFW” structure &amp;amp; root development!</em></li><li><em>Increases beneficial microbes!</em></li><li><em>Increases crop yield production!</em></li><li><em>Retains nourishment; holds water better!</em></li><li><em>Minimizes runoff &amp; potential for drought!</em></li><li><em>Improves fertility!</em></li><li><em>Remediates damage by crude oil, salt; mine tailing by removing heavy metals from water/soil!</em></li></ul>,<h2><em><strong>Applied science for Green Pastures AgriVillages with Soil Secrets:</strong></em></h2>,<ul><li><em>Agri-Enterprises</em></li><li><em>Landscapes</em></li><li><em>Construction</em></li><li><em>Parks &amp; Recreation</em></li><li><em>Land Rehabilitation &amp; Restoration</em></li><li><em>Bio-remediation</em></li></ul>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a40b13eb3d54779fe9bca6727e5f7d8b66e153cb.jpg" title="&quot;White Lightning&quot; featured product of Soil Secrets LLC" alt="White Lightning&reg; is a professional grade ultra-concentrated Mycorrhizal inoculant containing 9 species of beneficial fungi to promote growth.

This professional grade Mycorrhizal inoculant intentionally does not include other microorganisms, nor does it include bio-stimulants, as the intent of this product is to be a mycorrhizal inoculant only of the highest purity available! The viability, purity and high concentration of White Lightning&reg; ensures the highest degree of potential success.
 White Lightning&reg; contains Glomus intraradices an Arbuscular Mycorrhizae species and 8 species of Ectomycorrhizae. Individual species counts listed on reverse. Glomus intraradices associates with the vast majority of agricultural short term crops! Ectomycorrhizae associate with many conifers (i.e. hemlocks, firs and spruce) and hardwoods (i.e. pecans and oaks). For a complete list of plants and how they associate with, see our web site www.soilsecrets.com under the Details menu bar.">,<h3><em><strong>Healthy Soil = Healthy Food = Healthy Beings</strong></em></h3>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> offers this simple equation to educate citizens as to the necessity of understanding and supporting the “soil food web”! It is with great joy for Green Pastures Agrihoods to feature Soil Secrets.</p>,<p>This phenomenal premium product line realizes that the element of nitrogen is an essential ingredient of the “soil food web”! Soil microbes and plants live in a symbiotic relationship that requires nitrogen.</p>,<p>Nitrogen is a building block of amino acids, and, amino acids are the building blocks of protein! Supplying the “soil food web” with easily accessible and quality protein nutrients, such as Protein Crumblies® that contain “essential amino acids”, optimally nourishes the soil’s ecosystem in our precious earth! With optimal nourishing comes optimal flourishing!</p>,<h3><em><strong>TerraPro of Soil Secrets:</strong></em></h3>,<ul><li>Provides amino acids containing essential Nitrogen element!</li><li>Improves plant’s nutritional value!</li><li>Improves environmental sustainability</li><li>Increases crop yields!</li><li>Increases monetary revenue!</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/de543881-2307-430a-805a-632789fb4ba0.jpg" title="Why Do Your Plants Need Mycorrhizae Fungi?" alt="A mycorrhiza (from Greek &mu;&upsi;&kappa;&#x3CC;&sigmaf; myk&oacute;s, &quot;fungus&quot;, and &#x1FE5;&#x3AF;&zeta;&alpha; rhiza, &quot;root&quot;; pl. mycorrhizae or mycorrhizas) is a symbiotic association between a fungus and the roots of a vascular host plant.[1] The term mycorrhiza refers to the role of the fungi in the plants&apos; rhizosphere, its root system. Mycorrhizae play important roles in soil biology and soil chemistry.
In a mycorrhizal association, the fungus colonizes the host plant&apos;s root tissues, either intracellularly as in arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi (AMF or AM), or extracellularly as in ectomycorrhizal fungi. The association is generally mutualistic, but in particular species or in particular circumstances, mycorrhizae may be variously pathogenic in the host plants.[2]">,<h2><em><strong>Mycorrhizal Products</strong></em></h2>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> realizes the significance of mycorrhizal fungi for optimal and overall healthy soils! Mycorrhizal species of fungi are beneficial and essential to healthy soil components, such as the “soil food web”. “Myco” refers to “mushroom”, and “rhizal” refers to “related to roots”.</p>,<p>These benevolent fungi partner with many plants and trees. Their capability involves forming “exterior sheaths” symbiotically surrounding the root system for partnered plants (ectomycorrhizae). In addition, “Mycorrhizal fungi” seek the interior of “root cells” of “host plants” (endomycorrhizae).</p>,<p>Soil Secrets provides the highest quality and concentration of mycorrhizal soil treatments available on the market! EndoMaxima®, White Lightning®, and MycoMaxima® offer high quality, efficiency, effectiveness, and excellence with professional concentrated products. All products are available in large quantities.</p>,<p>Mycorrhizal fungi form a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutualism_(biology)" title="Mutualism (biology)">mutualistic </a>relationship with the roots of most plant species. In such a relationship, both the plants themselves and those parts of the roots that host the fungi, are said to be mycorrhizal. Relatively few of the mycorrhizal relationships between plant species and fungi have been examined to date, but 95% of the plant families investigated are predominantly mycorrhizal either in the sense that most of their species associate beneficially with mycorrhizae, or are absolutely dependent on mycorrhizae. The <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orchidaceae" title="Orchidaceae">Orchidaceae </a>are notorious as a family in which the absence of the correct mycorrhizae is fatal even to germinating seeds</p>,<p><strong>Mycorrhizal Fungal Benefits of Soil Secrets:</strong></p>,<ul><li><em>Builds topsoil for sequestering of essential carbon!</em></li><li><em>Increased crop yields!</em></li><li><em>Improved drought tolerance; sustainability!</em></li><li><em>Improved mineral nutrient uptake!</em></li><li><em>Improved food nutrient density!</em></li><li><em>Protects roots from damaging nematodes!</em></li><li><em>Improved ability to tolerate environmental stressors!</em></li><li><em>Increased profitability!</em></li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/af03cb4f-9f4e-4e3f-ae9c-b8fdca7f2ee9.jpg" title="ORGANIC FERTILIZERS
NATURE&rsquo;S BEST SOURCE OF NUTRITIONAL CALORIES FOR FEEDING THE SOIL." alt="Protein Crumblies&reg; is nature&rsquo;s best source of nutritional calories for feeding the soil. Derived from selected vegetable proteins, Soil Secrets has selected this product for the best ratios of amino acids that can provide the highest protein efficiency value possible. 

Soil Microorganisms are part of the &lsquo;Soil Food Web&rsquo; and Protein Crumblies can provide these microorganisms a high quality protein with the highest percent nitrogen per unit of protein. This product has a crude protein content providing a source of slow release organic nitrogen. The nitrogen can become part of the Soil Food Web once totally liberated by the action of the primary, secondary, and tertiary decomposers (soil microorganisms), and many plants can uptake the amino acids derived from this protein as part of their nitrogen budget.">,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7e5713e4055dc89064ca436d38eb5be6fa91c034.jpg" title="CLAY - HUMIC - COMPLEX">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ab8469a5-f1a1-4df5-838e-bc0b3a87a4e0.jpg" title="SOIL SECRETS CONSERVES WATER &amp; REPAIRS SOIL">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/16f6d2e4-fa08-4067-a203-f08889bfbb0d.jpg" title="SOIL SECRETS TEST SITE">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7f341dc0-b26a-404e-a7ee-580796f356f1.jpg" title="A SOIL HUMUS CONCENTRATE FOR SOIL CONDITIONING" alt="Earth Nectar&reg;: A super drink for the soil!   There&rsquo;s no question about it, microbes rule. They run all the major chemical cycles on earth by making enzymes that serve as catalysts to many of the important chemical reactions in the soil. 

Earth Nectar is a broad spectrum of soil based enzymes made by microbes. This product also contains TTP Supreme Compost, whole kelp, humus, and plant extracts, each dissolved into a rich nectar for the soil. Earth Nectar and Earth Ambrosia can be blended together in equal amounts, diluted with water and sprayed onto the soil as a drench. Do Not Use more than 1 gallon of either product per 1000 sq. ft. of application.">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/70856763-d95b-4a9a-b19f-71da27c31a1d.jpg" title="SOIL SECRETS SUGGESTS MINIMAL OR NO TILLAGE" alt="TTP Supreme Compost&reg;:  100% wholesome ingredients.  If made with quality ingredients and tight quality controls, compost can be an excellent source of organic nutrients. Never use a compost product without first examining the analysis of the product to see if it meets your needs. TTPSupreme Compost is a nutrient dense product that&rsquo;s been triple screened, providing a clean and fine particle size product, that&rsquo;s also clean enough to be used in hydroseeding equipment. City bio-solids (human waste) are not allowed in this product, which helps us guarantee you that disease contamination is minimized. This product has been tested by Western Labs for soil disease and has consistently tested clean and free of those risks. This product is nutrient dense and needs to be used sparingly, as a little goes a long way! A full assay of tests showing maturity, stability, Humic Acids, organic matter, nitrogen, major and minor nutrients, and carbon to nitrogen ratio is available upon request by emailing us as info@soilsecrets.com ">]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods-features-soil-secrets-premium-soil/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">af7e25fc-41e2-4d98-9163-eb375c565498</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 02:15:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GREEN PASTURES AGRIVILLAGES & HEMPHOODS]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<button data-role="cta">GREEN  PASTURES  AGRIVILLAGES  CONSULTATION</button>,<a href="https://www.facebook.com/GreenPastureAgriVillages/" data-role="cta">AgriVillages &amp; Hemphoods</a>,<h1><strong>GREEN PASTURES AGRIVILLAGES &amp; HEMPHOODS</strong></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/759975a1-a6ce-4935-b99c-1cec476e67a3.jpg" title="Flower of Life - Cosmic Fractal" alt="Fractal is a curve or geometric figure, each part of which has the same statistical character as the whole. Fractals are useful in modeling structures (such as eroded coastlines or snowflakes) in which similar patterns recur at progressively smaller scales, and in describing partly random or chaotic phenomena such as crystal growth, fluid turbulence, and galaxy formation.">,<h2><em>OVERVIEW: Green Pastures AgriVillages &amp; Hemphoods!</em></h2>,<p><strong>Green Pastures Agrihoods midwives accessible best practices of agri-stewardship on the local level with the support of MERF!</strong></p>,<p>Green Pastures Agrihoods mirror the legacy of Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.’s, ‘authentic loveservant leadership’, of the ‘1950s Freedom Movement’. King’s revolutionary approach of ‘creative covenantal beloved community’ and transformative love (‘inter-religious inter-ethical’) models ancient wisdom from most spiritual paths!</p>,<p>Through Green Pastures Agrihoods, there is a living and breathing model of beauty, excellence, efficiency with science bringing the best of all worlds together as a shining ‘prototype model example’!</p>,<p>Join this revolutionary effort by becoming a sister satellite location! Experience this phenomenal approach and solution-oriented science to bring nourishment and divine flourishment to the peoples of this wonderful planet, Mother Oceania-Earth! “Green Pastures Agrihoods” and “Hemphoods” is designed as part of a B-corp (beneficial corporation). This system is a type of ‘intentional cooperative system’ which benefits flow back into the village, neighborhood, and/or community!</p>,<p>“Green Pastures Agrihoods” and “Hemphoods” are the economic backbone for the 21st century global context! Agrihoods are agriculturally-based neighborhoods. Hemphoods are agri-culturally based neighborhoods, who are focused on industrial and medicinal hemp production. Both entities, are intentionally ‘zero waste and zero debt!</p>,<p><strong>Agrihoods as agriculturally-based neighborhoods are designed, cultivated, and nurtured based on community, land, and animal research analyses. It does include a needs-based assessment, with the underlying theme of sustainable living and agri-stewardship.</strong></p>,<p><strong>Optimally, ‘agrihoods’ serve to midwife basic human needs as determined by the neighborhood, village, or local community.</strong></p>,<h2><em><strong>Agrihood &amp; Hemphood Advantages &amp; Benefits</strong></em></h2>,<p>Benefits include:</p>,<ul><li>Stronger Local Community Connection</li><li>Fresh Heirloom Fruits &amp; Vegetables Locally Accessible</li><li>Entrepreneurialship &amp; Local Cottage Industries (Goods &amp; Services)</li><li>Zero Waste/Zero Debt for Basic Human Needs (5# Pillars)<ol><li><em><strong>Safe Sanctuary</strong></em></li><li><em><strong>Nutri-Nourishment</strong></em></li><li><em><strong>Adequate Clothing</strong></em></li><li><em><strong>Quality &amp; Simplified Communication</strong></em></li><li><em><strong>Green Transportation</strong></em></li></ol></li></ul>,<h2><em><strong>Community Sufficiency &amp; Self-Reliant Entrepreneurialship</strong></em></h2>,<p>Citizenry Benefits provide a methodology and mechanism by which, those who are willing to plug-in, to operate with consensus built-in, including a wholistic-minded philosophy and community self-reliance!</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e37502cf-6e79-4d3e-82ca-5473c152c867.jpg" title="Anatomy of the Industrial Hemp Stalk">,<p>Benefits include:</p>,<ol><li><strong>Sound Economic Leveraging for Wealth Legacy</strong></li><li><strong>Quality Products</strong></li><li><strong>Diversity of Goods &amp; Services</strong>*<em>Vertical Integration</em></li><li><strong>Accessibility, Innovation, Creativity, &amp; Flexibility</strong></li><li><strong>Efficient, Effective, &amp; Excellence</strong><em>*Citizen Education, Market Stability, Quality Assurance, Supply Stability &amp; Costs</em></li><li><strong>Lower Production &amp; Marketing Costs - Energy, Labor, Wealth-Sharing, Processing Costs, Increase &amp; Direct Revenue Sharing</strong></li><li><strong>Increased Bargaining Power, Price moderation, Direct to End-User, Reliable Supply Chain</strong></li><li><strong>Overall Increase in General Welfare</strong></li><li><strong>Local Resource Sharing</strong></li><li><strong>Increase in Ancillary Sector Support</strong></li><li><strong>Increase in Entrepreneurialship, Economic Literacy, &amp; Leadership Quality</strong><em>*Niche Marketing with Heirloom, nonGMO, Organic Provides Premium Pricing</em></li><li><strong>Satellite Support by ‘Emissary Ambassadors’</strong></li></ol>,<h2><em><strong>MODIFIED DELTEC HOME &amp; HEMP CONSTRUCTION</strong></em></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/acac317d-029e-45e0-8118-b9c256b0addd.jpg" title="DELTEC" alt="Our mission to create innovative, high-performance and net-zero energy homes with passion, excellence and respect for the natural world, has led us on an incredible journey. ... Today, over 85% of our homes are residential and best known for their energy efficiency and hurricane resistance.">,<h2><strong>VISION:</strong></h2>,<p>We will be the recognized leader of world class round homes and net-zero energy homes across the globe.</p>,<h3><em>VALUES:</em></h3>,<p><strong>EXCELLENCE: </strong>We hold ourselves and our products to the highest standards, never compromising in material quality, customer service, or craftsmanship.</p>,<p><strong>INNOVATION:</strong> We actively explore and integrate both new ideas and proven technologies to create superior value for our customers.</p>,<p><strong>INTEGRITY:</strong> We are dedicated to being honest and fair in all our interactions with others.</p>,<p><strong>PASSION:</strong> We believe what we do matters and take a great sense of pride in every home we create.</p>,<p><strong>ENVIRONMENTAL RESPONSIBILITY:</strong> We are committed to creating a positive and sustainable effect on our natural world.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a448f054-b579-4623-a3bb-74cf9a8d3b04.jpg" title="DELTEC SAVANNAH FLOOR PLAN" alt="Construction
From design to construction, customer experience is a top priority. We believe building a home shouldn&rsquo;t be a long, stressful process, which is why we&rsquo;ve designed our building system to be assembled quickly and easily. The precision-engineered components make it straightforward for any builder to put together. Since it&rsquo;s prefabricated in a climate-controlled factory, you don&rsquo;t have to be concerned about weather delays that most traditional builders experience.

Once shipped to your jobsite, the shell is placed on a permanent foundation, assembled&mdash;typically in five to seven days&mdash;and finished by your local builder. Our in-house 24-hour construction expert is available to answer any questions for your builder or we can provide an on-site technical assistant to guide the assembly of your shell.">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d73159fb-2de4-4b0b-aa92-1e731d256a86.jpg" title="DELTEC HOME INTERIOR LIVING SPACE" alt="Deltec Homes is a company that truly believes in customer satisfaction. Everyone has a great attitude and willing to do anything to be sure that you are left with a great customer experience.">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/212e925c-be9b-4be3-b44c-790144d4d9f5.jpg" title="DELTEC HOME IMAGE SHOWING AERODYNAMICS" alt="Founded in 1968, Deltec Homes is a family-owned company based out of Asheville, NC. We began as Delta Technologies and primarily built round homes for resort communities. As more and more guests of these resorts inquired about building their own round home, business shifted from commercial to residential. In 1985, founder Robert Kinser changed the name to Deltec Homes. Today, over 85% of our homes are residential and best known for their energy efficiency and hurricane resistance. Offering round, traditional and modern prefabricated kits, our homes are designed to provide a healthy and comfortable environment while protecting you and your family. Our commitment to excellence drives us to build each home to outperform all others in terms of quality, sustainability and strength. It&rsquo;s also this commitment that enabled us to receive our B Corporation Certification in 2016, an honor that verifies the commitment not only be the best in the world, but the best for the world.">,<h4><strong>Open web floor trusses are set in a radial pattern on your prepared foundation.</strong></h4>,<h4><strong>Timeline: The Basics of Building a Deltec home</strong></h4>,<p>Deltec’s process allows flexibility for all types of projects and customer schedules. </p>,<h3><strong>Net-Zero Energy</strong></h3>,<p>Our commitment to the environment drives us to build homes that not only reduce environmental impact, but create a restorative effect. The high performance design and advanced engineering make it easier and more attainable to build a home that produces as much energy as it needs through renewable energy, known as net-zero energy.</p>,<p>A net-zero home is more than a house with solar panels. It’s a house designed to put energy conservation first: from framing to finishing. Deltec’s airtight structural shell paired with our additional options—such as highly insulated wall systems, high performance windows, solar electric kits, passive solar design and more—mean any of our homes can easily achieve net-zero energy. With the&nbsp;<a href="http://www.deltechomes.com/our-homes/">Renew Collection</a>, many of those options are already built in, even further streamlining the process.</p>,<h2>The power of efficiency</h2>,<p>Trying to power a traditional home, especially an existing home, with enough renewable energy to make it net-zero, can be difficult. Deltec’s high performance shell is built to maximize energy efficiency before solar is added, making the addition of renewable energy—either now, or down the road—much more manageable. In addition, our RESNET HERS Rater is available to ensure you achieve your green building goals.</p>,<p><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong> is intentional about implementing modified Deltec home construction, using industrial hemp material integration, as much as possible (e.g. insulation, foundation, etc).</p>,<h2><em><strong>CONSENSUS: ‘Creative Covenantal Beloved Community’!</strong></em></h2>,<p>Green Pastures AgriVillages contextualizes, manifests in enriching King’s “Beloved Community”, as ‘Creative Covenantal Beloved Community’, from an Eco-Quare-Womanist theological perspective.</p>,<p>One key aspect is modeling consensus, within the community seeking to become a satellite of Green Pastures AgriVillages. Hall believes that long term community-sustainability demands that everyone vested and invested agrees on vital decision-making on behalf of the community. One representative will be the lead spokesperson and decision-maker, for those participating and vested families.</p>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a6412330765fd51135044d816a17e1e18936ce17.jpg" title="Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr." alt="From Agape International Spiritual Center">,<p>Hall expands King’s “The Beloved Community” by infusing a 21st century twist, in adding the modifier’s, ‘creative’ &amp; ‘covenantal’ with ‘Creative Covenantal Beloved Community’. In the 21st century global village, ‘creative’ or creativity is vital!</p>,<p>For Green Pastures Agrihoods, ‘creative’ includes criteria of innovative, accessible, simple, and sustainable! Zero waste and zero debt does require a creative approach, which will translate into community/self-reliance. 'Creative Covenantal Beloved Community' is manifested with the five pillars for Green Pastures Agrihoods and Hemphoods</p>,<p>Covenantal (adjective), or pertaining to the covenant (noun), literally refers to “an agreement, bargain; a sealed contract or clause as such a contract” to enter into a formal agreement (The New Lexicon Webster’s Dictionary of the English Language, Lexicon Publishing INC., New York, 1989 Edition). With Green Pastures Agrihoods, a covenant is necessary to assure the ultimate health and overall well being of the collective! This covenant primarily involves a commitment to consensus. Pertaining to the covenant of Green Pastures Agrihoods, the design hold intention surrounding the expression of ‘agape love’ is through <em>consensus</em>. King modeled an ‘authentic loveservant leadership’ in the Freedom Movement of the 20th century. This is the humanitarian and theological perspective of Green Pastures Agrihoods.</p>,<p><em>Consensus</em> is absolutely vital to augment the vitality of ‘Creative Covenantal Beloved Community’! Consensus incorporates supreme validity, when mutuality of all stakeholders have ‘honored voice’. Therefore, each ‘honored voice’ will be represented and heard. Everyone must agree. If agreement does not manifest, then it may be an opportunity to pause, for the greater good. Further, with consensus, no one is left outside of the circle.</p>,<h3><em><strong>Beloved Community</strong></em></h3>,<p>“The Beloved Community” is a term first coined in the early days of the 20th Century by the philosopher-theologian Josiah Royce, who founded the Fellowship of Reconciliation. However, it was Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., also a member of the Fellowship of Reconciliation, who popularized the term and invested it with a deeper meaning. This deeper meaning has captured the imagination of people of goodwill all over the world.</p>,<p>For Dr. King, The Beloved Community was not a lofty utopian goal to be confused with the rapturous image of the Peaceable Kingdom, in which lions and lambs coexist in idyllic harmony. Rather, The Beloved Community was for him a realistic, achievable goal that could be attained by a critical mass of people committed to and trained in the philosophy and methods of nonviolence.</p>,<p>Dr. King’s Beloved Community is a global vision, in which all people can share in the wealth of the earth. In the Beloved Community, poverty, hunger and homelessness will not be tolerated because international standards of human decency will not allow it. Racism and all forms of discrimination, bigotry and prejudice will be replaced by an all-inclusive spirit of sisterhood and brotherhood. In the Beloved Community, international disputes will be resolved by peaceful conflict-resolution and reconciliation of adversaries, instead of military power. Love and trust will triumph over fear and hatred. Peace with justice will prevail over war and military conflict.</p>,<p>Dr. King’s Beloved Community was not devoid of interpersonal, group or international conflict. Instead he recognized that conflict was an inevitable part of human experience. But he believed that conflicts could be resolved peacefully and adversaries could be reconciled through a mutual, determined commitment to nonviolence. No conflict, he believed, need erupt in violence. And all conflicts in The Beloved Community should end with reconciliation of adversaries cooperating together in a spirit of friendship and goodwill.</p>,<p>As early as 1956, Dr. King spoke of The Beloved Community as the end goal of nonviolent boycotts. As he said in a speech at a victory rally following the announcement of a favorable U.S. Supreme Court Decision desegregating the seats on Montgomery’s busses, “the end is reconciliation; the end is redemption; the end is the creation of the Beloved Community. It is this type of spirit and this type of love that can transform opponents into friends. It is this type of understanding goodwill that will transform the deep gloom of the old age into the exuberant gladness of the new age. It is this love which will bring about miracles in the hearts of men.”</p>,<h3><strong>Sustainable Agriculture &amp; Self-Reliance</strong></h3>,<p><strong>“George Washington Carver</strong> (1860s<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-nn-2">[2]</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-gwcnps-3">[3]</a> – January 5, 1943), was an American <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Botanist" title="Botanist">botanist</a> and inventor. The exact day and year of his birth are unknown; he was born into slavery in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Missouri" title="Missouri">Missouri</a>, either in 1861, or January 1864.<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-gwcnps-3">[3]</a></p>,<p>Carver's reputation is largely based on his promotion of alternative crops to cotton, such as <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peanut" title="Peanut">peanuts</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sweet_potatoes" title="Sweet potatoes">sweet potatoes</a>. He wanted poor farmers to grow alternative crops both as a source of their own food and as a source of other products to improve their quality of life. The most popular of his 44 practical bulletins for farmers contained 105 food recipes using peanuts. He spent years developing and promoting numerous products made from peanuts; none were commercially successful.<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-4">[4]</a> He was also a leader in promoting <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Environmentalism" title="Environmentalism">environmentalism</a>.<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-5">[5]</a> He received numerous honors for his work, including the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spingarn_Medal" title="Spingarn Medal">Spingarn Medal</a> of the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NAACP" title="NAACP">NAACP</a>.</p>,<p>In an era of very high racial polarization, his fame reached beyond the black community. He was widely recognized and praised in the white community for his many achievements and talents. In 1941, <em><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_(magazine)" title="Time (magazine)">Time</a></em> magazine dubbed Carver a "Black <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leonardo_da_Vinci" title="Leonardo da Vinci">Leonardo</a>".<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-time_article1-6">[6]</a></p>,<p>Carver developed techniques to improve soils depleted by repeated plantings of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cotton" title="Cotton">cotton</a>. Together with other agricultural experts, he urged farmers to restore <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nitrogen" title="Nitrogen">nitrogen</a> to their soils by practicing systematic <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crop_rotation" title="Crop rotation">crop rotation</a>: alternating cotton crops with plantings of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sweet_potatoes" title="Sweet potatoes">sweet potatoes</a> or <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Legumes" title="Legumes">legumes</a> (such as <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peanut" title="Peanut">peanuts</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soybean" title="Soybean">soybeans</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cowpea" title="Cowpea">cowpeas</a>). These crops both restored nitrogen to the soil and were good for human consumption. Following the crop rotation practice resulted in improved cotton yields and gave farmers alternative cash crops. To train farmers to successfully rotate and cultivate the new crops, Carver developed an agricultural extension program for Alabama that was similar to the one at Iowa State. To encourage better nutrition in the South, he widely distributed recipes using the alternative crops.</p>,<p>In addition, he founded an industrial research laboratory, where he and assistants worked to popularize the new crops by developing hundreds of applications for them. They did original research as well as promoting applications and recipes which they collected from others. Carver distributed his information as agricultural bulletins.</p>,<h3><strong>Peanut specimen collected by Carver</strong></h3>,<p>Carver's work was known by officials in the national capital before he became a public figure. President <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Theodore_Roosevelt" title="Theodore Roosevelt">Theodore Roosevelt</a> publicly admired his work. Former professors of Carver's from Iowa State University were appointed to positions as Secretary of Agriculture: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Wilson_(U.S._politician)" title="James Wilson (U.S. politician)">James Wilson</a>, a former dean and professor of Carver's, served from 1897 to 1913. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Henry_Cantwell_Wallace" title="Henry Cantwell Wallace">Henry Cantwell Wallace</a> served from 1921 to 1924. He knew Carver personally because his son <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Henry_A._Wallace" title="Henry A. Wallace">Henry A. Wallace</a> and the researcher were friends.<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-29">[29]</a> The younger Wallace served as U.S. Secretary of Agriculture from 1933 to 1940, and as <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franklin_Delano_Roosevelt" title="Franklin Delano Roosevelt">Franklin Delano Roosevelt</a>'s vice president from 1941 to 1945.</p>,<p>The American industrialist, farmer, and inventor <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Edenborn" title="William Edenborn">William Edenborn</a> of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Winn_Parish,_Louisiana" title="Winn Parish, Louisiana">Winn Parish</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louisiana" title="Louisiana">Louisiana</a>, grew peanuts on his demonstration farm. He consulted with Carver.<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver#cite_note-30">[30]</a></p>,<p>In 1916 Carver was made a member of the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Royal_Society_of_Arts" title="Royal Society of Arts">Royal Society of Arts</a> in England, one of only a handful of Americans at that time to receive this honor. Carver's promotion of peanuts gained him the most notice. In 1919, Carver wrote to a peanut company about the potential he saw for peanut milk. Both he and the peanut industry seemed unaware that in 1917 William Melhuish had secured <a href="https://worldwide.espacenet.com/textdoc?DB=EPODOC&amp;IDX=US1243855">US 1243855</a>, issued 1917-10-23for a milk substitute made from peanuts and soybeans.[<em><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:No_original_research#Synthesis_of_published_material" title="Wikipedia:No original research">improper synthesis?</a></em>]</p>,<p>The United Peanut Associations of America invited Carver to speak at their 1920 convention. He discussed "The Possibilities of the Peanut" and exhibited 145 peanut products. By 1920, the U.S. peanut farmers were being undercut by low prices on imported peanuts from the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Republic_of_China" title="Republic of China">Republic of China</a>.</p>,<p>In 1921 peanut farmers and industry representatives planned to appear at Congressional hearings to ask for a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tariff" title="Tariff">tariff</a>. Based on the quality of Carver's presentation at their convention, they asked the African-American professor to testify on the tariff issue before the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/House_Ways_and_Means_Committee" title="House Ways and Means Committee">Ways and Means Committee</a> of the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_House_of_Representatives" title="United States House of Representatives">United States House of Representatives</a>. Due to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Racial_segregation" title="Racial segregation">segregation</a>, it was highly unusual for an African American to appear as an expert witness at Congress representing European-American industry and farmers. Southern congressmen, reportedly shocked at Carver's arriving to testify, were said to have mocked him.[<em><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Citation_needed" title="Wikipedia:Citation needed">citation needed</a></em>] As he talked about the importance of the peanut and its uses for American agriculture, the committee members repeatedly extended the time for his testimony. The <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fordney-McCumber_Tariff" title="Fordney-McCumber Tariff">Fordney-McCumber Tariff</a> of 1922 was passed including one on imported peanuts. Carver's testifying to Congress made him widely known as a public figure” (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Washington_Carver).</p>,<p><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong> embraces the legacy of both King and Carver, bringing their legacies forward into the 21st century global context.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods-and-hemphoods/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">607a47ba-ac06-4bc5-aea1-17b17568d58b</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 21:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages - ZeroWaste Landscaping & Compost]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages - ZeroWaste Landscaping &amp; Compost</strong></h1>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> provides a local community service for ‘ZeroWast Landscaping &amp; Compost’.</p>,<p>Way too much food is wasted each year! Estimates total approximate at 40 million tons! ZeroWaste Landscaping &amp; Compost is committed to a solution.</p>,<p>ZeroWaste Landscaping &amp; Compost serves homeowners and local business in creating both landscapes and aquascapes, which promote healthy food production along with native ecosystems/plants.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ea1a44c6-d8ec-4b65-895c-9bf43763389f.jpg" title="Food Waste Pile" alt="USA has over 40 millions tons of food waste!">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/190a71ef-51a2-4bef-bff5-5ebb614724a1.jpg" title="We are marching towards a Zero Waste world!" alt="Elephants moving humans forward toward zero waste. Join us on the journey!">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b5dc71d8-eac2-4c43-b2d3-6247f3790015.jpg" title="ZERO WASTE CHALLENGE">,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2d74a7c5cf7532954c2d820c5fad3c90ab2e1c4c.jpg" title="10 STEPS TO ZERO WASTE">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c2f94409-146d-4fd1-9fcd-848161cab045.jpg" title="PRODUCE WASTE" alt="Fresh fruits &amp; vegetables headed to the landfill">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c4b32590-c286-4186-b1c6-9a7738b9d94d.jpg" title="Common Landfill in the USA" alt="When was the last time you visited a landfill near you?">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c4f5734f-5191-44f3-93d9-381cedf0d15b.jpg" title="Reuse, Reduce, Repurpose, Recycle" alt="Different colored containers for recycling">,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e896ea1616e95f80984cb649bd5231ab8c57d80d.jpg" title="IT IS NOT WASTED, UNTIL IT IS WASTED!">,<p>This benevolent company seeks local retailers and municipalities to recycle food waste, then provide composting it into natural, organic and sustainable garden soils.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods-zerowaste-landscaping-and-compost/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c21dd26f-79d4-4c12-8292-d195fa0cb5f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 17:32:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages: Caprine & Small Ruminant Production]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<button data-role="cta">Caprine Production</button>,<h1><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages: Caprine &amp; Small Ruminant Production</strong></em></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a9196fe1-3559-4701-bbbf-8e4f5b035a0e.jpg">,<h2>Caprine Meat Production: Chevron</h2>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> will focus primarily on meat, then dairy goat production for self-reliance.</p>,<p>Caprine production offers three options:</p>,<ul><li>Meat (Cabrito for Latino Populations, 1 year&gt;; Chevron for Middle Eastern Populations, 1 year &lt;)</li><li>Dairy (Only for the family)</li><li>Fibre</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/df9f8cd8-5cdf-435e-b196-dd3ce6aca6bc.jpg">,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> holds top breeding pairs of the Nubian breed of milk goat. Goat milk has many attributes for self-reliant agrivillages! The milk is known to be universally accepted for humans and pet animal companions in need of ‘nutri-nourishment’ in order to assist with a thriving newborn.</p>,<p>One moderately producing milk doe is quite enough to support a family of four. Regarding dairy production, the Nubian breed is most optimal!</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/857eb89b-8921-40fd-9581-2d6c1688ea27.jpg">,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> holds top breeding pairs of the Kiko meat goat. In reference to meat production, the Kiko breed is most optimal animal. In order to implement effective, efficient, &amp; excellent outcomes, goats provide the features in the ‘agrivillages prototype’ that is duplicatable in most locations. These animals are hardy, and the ability to apply animal husbandry is simple to manage for women and children!</p>,<p>The choice for goat production is completely intentional. It is possible to create a doubling of a herd within a year’s time, for the pregnancy timeframe is 4 months, where twins are usually borne!</p>,<p>Chevron or ‘goat meat’ is the mostly consumed meat product in the world!</p>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> promotes and supports the implementation of caprine production. Contact Dr. Hall for caprine herd health consultation.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods-caprine-and-small-ruminant-productio/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1217dd62-1f47-4f35-bae9-eb6e3ba02ec7</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 02:15:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages & Benevolent Mushrooms - Ganoderma]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<button data-role="cta">Benevolent Mushrooms</button>,<h1><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages &amp; Benevolent Mushrooms - </strong><em><strong>Ganoderma</strong></em></h1>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures Agrihoods</strong></em> intentionally supports benevolent mushroom production, using the <em>Ganoderma</em> spp.</p>,<p><em>Ganoderma lucidum</em> is the genus and species of choice for Green Pastures Agrihoods.</p>,<p><em><strong>“Ganoderma </strong></em>is a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Genus" title="Genus">genus </a>of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polypore" title="Polypore">polypore </a>mushrooms that grow on wood, and include about 80 species, many from <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tropical" title="Tropical">tropical </a>regions.Because of their extensive use in traditional Asian medicines, and their potential in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bioremediation" title="Bioremediation">bioremediation</a>, they are a very important genus economically. <em>Ganoderma </em>can be differentiated from other polypores because they have a double-walled <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Basidiospore" title="Basidiospore">basidiospore</a>. They are popularly referred to as shelf mushrooms or <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bracket_fungus" title="Bracket fungus">bracket fungi</a>.” [1, https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ganoderma]</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/29e364ec-fcd3-456c-b05f-98ea915849e7.jpg" title="Ganoderma spp." alt="Growing in logs">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bec15fd4-2c00-4394-984a-e07174fb3041.jpg" title="Benefits of Ganoderma">,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/661942ce09bbba9899d5c8128b73d7f6a6954de2.jpg" title="Health Benefits of Ganoderma">,<p><em>“Ganoderma </em>are characterized by <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Basidiocarp" title="Basidiocarp">basidiocarps </a>that are large, perennial, woody brackets also called "<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Conk_(fungus)" title="Conk (fungus)">conks</a>". They are <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wood-decay_fungus" title="Wood-decay fungus">lignicolous </a>and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coriaceous" title="Coriaceous">leathery </a>either with or without a stem. The fruit bodies typically grow in a fan-like or hoof-like form on the trunks of living or dead trees. They have double-walled, truncate <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spore" title="Spore">spores </a>with yellow to brown ornamented inner layers.” [2, https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ganoderma]</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods-and-benevolent-mushrooms-ganoderma/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">48e68456-8e73-4365-aab0-17dda62bf721</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 02:15:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages: Specialty Crop - Lavender]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages: Specialty Crop - Lavender</strong></h1>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> holds benevolent intentionality surrounding the decision to incorporate lavender as a specialty crop.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f5144667-3118-40be-8815-256d016456fa.jpg">,<p>Lavender is a small, aromatic shrub used in the fragrance, specialty food, and alter-native medicine industries. Although family farmers may find large-scale extraction of lavender’s valuable oil too expensive and laborious, small-scale lavender production is feasible for some farmers using alternative marketing strategies. Entertainment farming has been a very successful form of alternative marketing for lavender, especially as a focus for annual festivals and product sales.</p>,<p>Like most herbs, lavender has few if any insect pests. Few fungal diseases attack lavender, but since there are no known remedies for them, chemical applications are not an issue. Lavender ranks high as a sustainable crop because it does not rely on pesticides and fertilizers. It does not require fertilizing, although in rare circumstances irrigation may be called for. The biggest issue is finding a viable marketing method.</p>,<p><em><strong>“Lavandula angustifolia</strong></em> (<strong>lavender</strong> most commonly <strong>true lavender</strong> or <strong>English lavender</strong>, though not native to England; also <strong>garden lavender</strong>,<strong>common lavender</strong>, <strong>narrow-leaved lavender</strong>), formerly <em>L. officinalis</em>, is a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/w/index.php?title=Flowering_%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88_plants&amp;action=edit&amp;redlink=1" title="Flowering الو plants (page does not exist)">flowering الو plants</a> in the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Family_(biology)" title="Family (biology)">family</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lamiaceae" title="Lamiaceae">Lamiaceae</a>, native to the Mediterranean (Spain, France, Italy, Croatia etc.).</p>,<h2>Growth</h2>,<p>Flower spike before the petals emergeCalyx (purple) and flower bracts (light brown)Calyx and corollaCorolla (petals)Calyx and corolla</p>,<p>It is a strongly aromatic <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shrub" title="Shrub">shrub</a> growing as high as 1 to 2 metres (3.3 to 6.6 ft) tall. The leaves are <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evergreen" title="Evergreen">evergreen</a>, 2–6 centimetres (0.79–2.36 in) long, and 4–6 millimetres (0.16–0.24 in) broad. The flowers are pinkish-purple (lavender-coloured), produced on spikes 2–8 cm (0.79–3.15 in) long at the top of slender, leafless stems 10–30 cm (3.9–11.8 in) long.</p>,<h2>Etymology</h2>,<p>The <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Species" title="Species">species</a> name <em>angustifolia</em> is Latin for "narrow leaf". Previously, it was known as <em>Lavandula <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Officinalis" title="Officinalis">officinalis</a></em>, referring to its medicinal properties.</p>,<h2>Cultivation</h2>,<p>English lavender is commonly grown as an <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ornamental_plant" title="Ornamental plant">ornamental plant</a>. It is popular for its colourful flowers, its fragrance, and its ability to survive with low water consumption. It does not grow well in continuously damp soil and may benefit from increased drainage provided by inorganic mulches such as gravel. It does best in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mediterranean_climate" title="Mediterranean climate">Mediterranean climates</a> similar to its native habitat, characterised by wet winters and dry summers. It is fairly tolerant of low temperatures and is generally considered hardy to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USDA" title="USDA">USDA</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hardiness_zone" title="Hardiness zone">zone 5</a>.It tolerates acid soils but favours neutral to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alkali_soils" title="Alkali soils">alkaline soils</a>, and in some conditions it may be short-lived.” (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lavandula_angustifolia)</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods-specialty-crop-lavender/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">62f8b73b-3db8-48d8-9c7e-1faaeec84cd4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Pastures AgriVillages: Industrial Hemp & Intentional Construction Development]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<button data-role="cta">Hemp Espirit de Corps</button>,<h1><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages: Industrial Hemp &amp; Intentional Construction Development</strong></em></h1>,<p><em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em> has chosen industrial hemp as a specialty crop. Industrial hemp holds infinite applications. The primary purpose for hemp production, for <em><strong>Green Pastures AgriVillages</strong></em>, is for intentional and sustainable construction.</p>,<p>Intentional communities using hemp construction is the creative and necessary innovation for 21st century global agrihoods - neighborhoods, villages, &amp; small communities!</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ec664060-44fc-489d-bcc1-a674f6fc9ee6.jpg" title="Industrial Hemp Field">,<p>“Hemp includes all varieties of the Cannabis genus that contain negligible amounts of THC (a component of the cannabis plant that can be intoxicating when heated).”[1, <em>Hemp Bound</em> by Doug Fine, p. xix] THC is the acronym for tetrahydrocannabidiol, and is the psychoactive component for recreational use of this plant. Hemp is synonymous with “industrial cannabis”. [2, <em>Hemp Bound</em> by Doug Fine, p. xix]</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/874b1c25-3799-470e-b0a6-4768dc8551fa.jpg" title="HARVEST TIME!" alt="Industrial hemp being harvested, by hand">,<p>“Cannabis is a dioecious plant (there are males and females), and branches are covered with hand-like leaf fans.”[3, <em>Hemp Bound</em> by Doug Fine, p. xix] “Originated in Central Asia, hemp has a four to six month growing cycle and has been successfully cultivated on every continent except Antarctica.” [4, <em>Hemp Bound</em> by Doug Fine, p. xix-xxii]</p>,<p>“Mature plants range from two to twelve”, or more feet. [5, <em>Hemp Bound</em> by Doug Fine, p. xxii]</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f0ddec2b-dd0f-4c39-9009-4896f10a6187.jpg" title="HEMPCRETE" alt="Showing the revolutionary benefits with hemp as a construction material">,<ul><li>A hemp crop can be grown without the use of herbicides or insecticides.</li><li>Hemp produces up to four tonnes of material per acre per year.</li><li>It is especially suited to organic sustainable agriculture.</li><li>Hemp is categorized as a bast fibre crop.</li><li>It has a stem consisting of an outer skin containing long strong fibres surrounding a hollow wood core.This woody core is of a very open sponge like structure. (HempBuilding.com)</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/45700143-d98e-4451-817a-75ff1eecfd12.jpg" title="Hemp Stalk" alt="The cross-sectional anatomy of a hemp stalk">,<ul><li>After processing the stems, two materials are produced; hurds and fibres.</li><li>Both hurds and fibres have properties that make them useful in building construction. (HempBuilding.com)</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/eb565bd7-ac93-4f24-ac99-e5678d03fe48.png" title="SAVE THE FOREST, PLANT A HEMP FARM" alt="Hemp is the strongest building material in the world!">,<ul><li>Hemp hurds are mixed with a combination of lime products to produce a light weight, insulating, breathing material.</li><li>The mixture of lime to hurds varies with the type of construction application and prevailing climatic conditions. (HempBuilding.com)</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ae9cc866-ba3c-4cb5-a586-af68336df3a1.jpg" title="Hemp Home">,<ul><li>This hempcrete is cast around a framework.</li><li>This is achieved by <a href="javascript:openIt('tamp.html');" title="Tamping">tamping down</a> between shuttering, or it can be sprayed against a formwork (permanent or temporary).</li><li>Internally a variety of finishes are possible. In this example the framework has been left exposed and the hempcrete finished with a natural paint. (HempBuilding.com</li></ul>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e0247618-d558-4621-9dae-d6b2232930de.jpg" title="Hemp Housing Construction" alt="Dome home built with industrial hemp">,<p>Externally the hempcrete is finished with a lime render, which can be painted with breathable natural paints.</p>,<p>“Hempcrete in twelve inch thick sections has an R-value…of twenty (20#).” [1, <em>HempBound</em> by Doug Fine, p,33-34] Hemp insulation “takes less” energy, and will “keep a house heated to seventy degrees Fahrenheit (70 F/21 C)”. [2, <em>HempBound</em> by Doug Fine, p,33-34]</p>,<p>Hempcrete is “easy to apply on-site…, is caste around a” framework of support. [3, HempBound by Doug Fine, p,33-34]</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/green-pastures-agrihoods/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">93bdee85-def5-4f94-b159-9d182872c0c5</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 17:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WELLNESS MOBILE VETERINARY CLINIC]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><em><strong>WELLNESS MOBILE VETERINARY CLINIC</strong></em></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0b9c7d44-1114-48ac-9280-f0d3425454e3.png" title="Wellness Mobile Veterinary Clinic" alt="Wholistic veterinary methods refer to those which are applied with the entire being (e.g. Human, Animal) as the priority
consideration.
Integrative veterinary methods refer all ancient wisdom medicine and healing techniques of indigenous cultures (e.g.
Traditional Chinese Medicine/TCM) and current traditional medicinal techniques (e.g. surgery in western medicine).
As a veterinarian who practices with a context of &ldquo;Wholistic Integrative&rdquo;, it is appropriate to share the significance of the
health of the healer. Healers must learn how to not only &lsquo;heal self&rsquo;, but also maintain optimal overall health and
wellness. Embracing the understanding of being a healer includes being a teacher. Teacher is the underlying context of
which the understanding of &ldquo;physician&rdquo; rose. Uphold the &lsquo;healer-teacher&rsquo; mindset, and employ a minimum of three (3#)
spiritual techniques or disciplines by which one embraces the mindfulness of becoming &lsquo;one who heals&rsquo;!">,<h2><em><strong>Wholistic Integrative Energy-Based Veterinary Medicine</strong></em></h2>,<p>1)<em> Ayuvedic Veterinary Medicine</em></p>,<p>The earliest information on the art of caring for animals in India is provided by the sacred texts of the Vedic religion. These texts, written between 1500 and 600 BC, were transmitted orally from generation to generation, over the centuries, before being written down. The oldest Vedic literature consists of collections of hymns, liturgical chants and sacrificial or magical formulae, mainly in verse, which constitute the Veda proper (1500-1000 BC).</p>,<p>2) <em>Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) – Chi Institute; International Veterinary Acupuncture Society</em></p>,<p>Traditional Chinese Veterinary Medicine (TCVM), although relatively new to the Western world, is a medical system used in China to treat animals for thousands of years.&nbsp; It is an adaptation and extension of Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) used to treat humans.&nbsp; Speaking broadly, Chinese Medicine is a complete body of thought and practice grounded in Chinese Daoist philosophy.&nbsp; Though it can be traced back over two millennia in recorded history, it, like any medical system, continues to evolve today, and current research on acupuncture and herbal medicine is beginning to shed light on its mechanism of action.</p>,<p>3) <em>‘Nutri-Nourishment’ is minimally 90% of overall health and wellness! (</em>VETERINARY FORMULAS ™ Standard Process)</p>,<p>Standard Process holds a line of Veterinary Formulas that are vital to wholistic veterinary medical practice. At this time in our collective evolution, both humans and animals must supplement due to the commercialized, mechanized, monetized, and industrialized approach to food/animal production. Mother Earth’s soils have been depleted. ‘Nutri-nourishment’ is essential to survive as well as thrive!</p>,<p>Muscle Response Testing is a technique which allows for clients to be a surrogate for their animals to survey the body in order to ask the ‘physical body temple’ what is needed and where from a nutritional standpoint.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/549f87d8-52cc-4b3d-b880-1ac33a40a8f4.jpg" title="Sophia &amp; Dr. Hall" alt="

1) Nutri-Nourishment  2) Acupuncture 3) Animal Chiropractic 4) Essential Oils
5) Homeopathy 6) Light Therapy, Massage &amp; Other Energy Healing Techniques
(*Healing Touch * Reiki *BEMER) 7) Massage, Training, &amp; Grooming

">]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/wellness-mobile-veterinary-clinic/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b0fae851-075a-4071-9154-2d86cf0141d7</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 15:26:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Collaborators & Partners]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Business Collaborators &amp; Partners</strong></h1>,<h2><strong>KARATBARS INTERNATIONAL</strong></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c3781ba9-2961-40a3-857a-8779b152c683.png" title="Karatbars International" alt="Karatbars International was founded in 2011. The company specializes in the sale of small gold bars and gift items in gold bullion.

The headquarters and the logistics center of Karatbars International is located in Stuttgart, Germany. It is responsible for the support, marketing, customer and partner communication, execution and delivery of orders. Headquarters also co-ordinates the opening of new countries throughout Europe.

Deliveries in smaller quantities are packaged under video surveillance at the headquarters of Karatbars International, and shipped daily via FedEx.

Partner Shipment Companies:
FedEx

Gold Production: 
Nadir Gold (Turkey),">,<h3><em><strong>Prelude</strong></em></h3>,<p>All Karatbars International employees contribute, through their actions, to the image of Karatbars’ partners and clients all over the world. We at Karatbars International believe that maintaining a strong reputation is greatly influenced by the reliable and trustworthy work of all our employees.</p>,<p>Our mission - to serve our clients in uniformity and direction, entailing strong, transparent communication processes (to best serve our customers and our ideals on dealing with colleagues and partners).</p>,<p>Our goal - to always find and implement new methods that perpetuate the improvement of Karatbars International in every avenue of the industry.</p>,<h2><em><strong>BEMER</strong></em></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f54510a0-ba28-427c-abf9-fc47419c8ded.jpg" title="BIO-ELEKTRO-MAGNETISCHE ENERGIE-REGULATION" alt="Organic Electro-Magnetic Energy Regulation available for both humans &amp; animals">,<p><strong>BEMER</strong>: <strong>BEMER</strong> stands for Bio Electro-Magnetic Energy Regulation “Electromagnetic energy is known as the oldest form of energy in the universe. Since the beginning, nature has produced this form of energy as the basis for the proper functioning of all organisms.” Peter Gleim, president of Inomad International AG, the manufacturing corporation of the <strong>BEMER</strong>, a pulsed magnetic field device.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e63196df-a0d8-4a7c-a2f2-f1399617af87.jpg" title="BEMER VETERINARY DEVICE">,<h3><em><strong>Where is BEMER made and what are the certifications?</strong></em></h3>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5f38bca0-ad85-4bfc-b5c6-0bc1373759eb.jpg" title="BEMER VET HORSE BLANKET">,<h3>The <strong>BEMER</strong> is manufactured in Liechtenstein and has been on the market for over 10 years. It is sold in 42 countries world wide. In Europe, the <strong>BEMER</strong> has a highly respected certification in its classification as a Medical Device IIA.</h3>,<h3>No complaints of adverse side effects of the <strong>BEMER</strong> have been reported to the governing World Health Organization, who set European guidelines for public exposure to electromagnetic frequencies.</h3>,<h3>The <strong>BEMER</strong> corporation in America was recently awarded an IRB # by the FDA. It is the only company in the US that has been given this number, allowing medical doctors in the U.S. To use the device in their practice and bill the insurance companies.</h3>,<h3><strong>Cooperation Agreement with NASA signed!</strong></h3>,<p>Our engineers, scientists and application experts are working directly with renowned scientific institutes and universities in Europe and North America.</p>,<h2><em><strong>RxCBD</strong></em></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/340e1b2d-2c70-4225-9e9b-451268c97c1a.jpg" title="RxCBD " alt="Provides medicinal cannabis for animal pet companions! (https://www.rxcbd.co/)">,<p>We are a business that r<strong>ecognizes the value of natural products</strong> &amp; <strong>believes in the power of alternative medicine.</strong><br>Our Contributors possess a wide range of knowledge and experience: Microbiologist, Engineer, Holistic Health Practitioner, Master Baker, Animal Care &amp; Nutrition!</p>,<h2><em><strong>ZIJA &amp; MORINGA</strong></em></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/52791893-e566-4608-b35c-6d752224af5c.jpg" title="ZIJA" alt="Zija International was founded on the idea that a better life is possible with the right combination of products, opportunity, timing and endeavor. Our cutting-edge health, wellness and beauty products allow individuals to look and feel their best, be more active, and share the Natural Health Revolution. The unique and simple Zija opportunity provides unprecedented financial and time freedom to countless individuals worldwide. We invite everyone to bring their all and become their best, stretching and growing in the journey toward building their own Life Unlimited.

- Zija International Mission Statement">,<h3><strong>MORINGA</strong></h3>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3ade840f-e2d9-44a6-843e-2a7ebf41a9f4.jpg" title="CORE MORINGA SuperMix" alt="BOTANIC DESCRIPTION Moringa oleifera is a small, graceful, deciduous tree with sparse foliage, often resembling a leguminous species at a distance, especially when in flower, but immediately recognized when in fruit. The tree grows to 8 m high and 60 cm dbh.">,<p><strong>Moringa</strong> (<em>Moringa oleifera</em>Lam.) is a multipurpose tropical tree. It is mainly used for food and has numerous industrial, medicinal and agricultural uses, including animal feeding. Nutritious, fast-growing and drought-tolerant, this traditional plant was rediscovered in the 1990s and its cultivation has since become increasingly popular in Asia and Africa, where it is among the most economically valuable crops. It has been dubbed the "miracle tree" or "tree of life" by the media (<a href="https://www.feedipedia.org/node/19283">FAO, 2014</a>;<a href="https://www.feedipedia.org/node/19285">Radovich, 2009</a>;<a href="https://www.feedipedia.org/node/1650">Orwa et al., 2009</a>;<a href="https://www.feedipedia.org/node/19284">Bosch, 2004</a>).</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/919c5e12-d3d4-4a42-b99c-55db66cbf7de.jpg" title="OFFICIAL MEDICINE HAS PROVED MORINGA BENEFITS">,<h2><em><strong>STANDARD PROCESS</strong></em></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/78443077-5182-49b3-b071-b2ac5802d821.jpg" title="Standard Process" alt="&quot;Standard Process is devoted to improving the quality of life by providing the safest, most effective, hight-quality dietary supplements through health care professionals.&quot; ... Coming Soon - The Nutrition Unlimited online store, serving our customers needs and a global need to empower everyone to live a healthy lifestyle. (And make sure to use our account number at checkout: C017549)">,<p>Our time-tested formulas with whole food ingredients provide safe, effective, high-quality nutritional support. Available through health care professionals, our products promote a better quality of life for patients.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7c559c2e-2483-4ee2-8096-f8b95b74c573.jpg" title="Standard Process Veterinary Formulas" alt="For more than 85 years, Standard Process has made nutritional supplements with whole food ingredients for people. ... We created our Veterinary Formulas&trade; supplements specifically for animals. Using these products, a veterinarian can recommend safe, high-quality nutritional support for your dogs, cats, and horses.">,<h2><strong>HOST DEFENSE</strong></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bff8a286-d88b-40f7-a77b-30f4e0b168bd.jpg" title="HOST DEFENSE" alt="At Host Defense, we are dedicated to protecting the environment. We all know that environmental health and human health are directly interrelated.">,<h3><strong>Your support of Host Defense® helps on this global mission to:</strong></h3>,<p>1. <em>We are a family-owned company specializing in functional food mushroom supplements to support natural immunity and whole body wellness.*</em></p>,<p><em>2. We pioneer strategies to counter Colony Collapse Disorder and save bees using mushrooms and fungi.</em></p>,<p><em>3. We teach about growing mushrooms for food on wood, straw, and other repurposed waste materials.</em></p>,<p><em>4. We protect the biodiversity of fungi along with the plants and animals that depend on them.&nbsp;</em></p>,<p><em>5. We develop mycofiltration methods to clean water using mycelium.<br>(Photo credit: Katherine Ball's mycofilters lower E. coli on Indianapolis Island)</em></p>,<p><em>6.We build soil with beneficial fungi to support plant and animal food webs, aiding agriculture, forests, and ecosystems.</em></p>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/aef688a823e07288919610483f39989e/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=300&cropwidth=564&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Faecc2114-9b68-4b85-8537-6b8d551ee653.jpg&x=16&y=0" title="GIVE BEES A CHANCE" alt="Host Defense&reg; mushrooms are grown on our farm at Kamilche Point, Washington State. We maintain organic growing conditions to maintain a pure, contaminant-free mushroom harvest. We practice sustainable cultivation, which protects wild species and their environments. A portion of Host Defense proceeds goes to research to save rare strains of mushrooms that dwell within old growth forests. We maintain control over all growing and harvesting processes.">,<p><strong>What is BeeFriendly™?</strong>BeeFriendly™&nbsp;is a Host Defense®&nbsp;initiative to help reverse the&nbsp;devastating declines in the global&nbsp;bee population that are critically&nbsp;threatening the world’s food security.</p>,<p><strong>Why do bees need help?&nbsp;</strong>In 2015, Colony Collapse Disorder (CCD) rates increased 6% to affect&nbsp;<strong>41%</strong>&nbsp;of managed bee colonies nationwide. Some scientists estimate that all managed bee colonies could face total decimation by CCD within five years. Although CCD is not fully understood, it appears to be a destructive synergism of multiple factors. Pathogen (bacterial &amp; viral) infection harms bees already challenged by other stress factors: parasitic mites, pesticides, fungicides and GMO exposure. These stressors of infection, parasitism, toxins, and immune deficits/depression may initiate CCD.</p>,<p><strong>Why Host Defense?</strong><br>Bees need comprehensive immune&nbsp;support to combat the diseases,&nbsp;parasites, and toxins that are driving&nbsp;their decline. Supporting Host&nbsp;Defense means supporting bee&nbsp;recovery research and development.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://agrihoodsglobal.com/business-collaborators-and-partners/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2c4b2333-abe3-46c4-a4a7-1ccdafdf8ad7</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 02:15:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>